<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
	<ui:style>
		.important {
			font-weight: bold;
		}
	</ui:style>
	<g:HTMLPanel>
		<div id="body-text">
			<p>
				BooksPicker grew out of our own frustrations as students buying 
				books. The COOP's prices were absurdly high, and the process of 
				buying books elsewhere was time-consuming and tedious, especially 
				when we wanted to compare offers between online merchants and 
				students.
				<br />
				<br />
				But above all we did not like the fact that we could not just 
				enter the classes we were taking and based on that find the books 
				we needed. We thought that this should be an easy task, since The 
				COOP had all the information, but we were wrong. We found out 
				that The COOP was unwilling to share the information with anyone 
				(including MIT). Apparently they obtain the information directly 
				from the faculty, without going through an in-house MIT channel.
				<br />
				<br />
				We thought this situation was unacceptable, so we decided to fight
				for the freedom of the information (and this is why we are pirates).
				We wrote an 
				<a href="http://tech.mit.edu/V129/N35/letters.html" target="_blank">article on The Tech</a>
				and started a discussion with many groups at MIT, including faculty,
				IS&amp;T, and MIT Libraries. Our efforts and the Higher Education
				Opportunity Act of 2008, which requires all educational institutions
				provide such textbook information by June 2010, served as catalysts
				for MIT to
				<a href="http://web.mit.edu/newsoffice/2010/textbook-update.html" target="_blank">enhance its Online Textbook Information (OTI) system</a>.
				As such, MIT now makes book information available to anyone,
				including services such as the course catalog and Stellar.
				The information provided by OTI is still incomplete, but we are
				happy that things are moving in the right direction. And even though
				our main fight is over, we are still here to serve you and provide
				you with the best experience for buying and selling your textbooks.
				<br />
				<br />
				BooksPicker was built by a group of three MIT students (Jonathan
				Goldberg, Sinchan Banerjee, and Rodrigo Ipince) with the advice of
				Professor David Karger.
				<br />
				<br />
				We love feedback. If you have some, send it to us at bookspicker at
				mit.edu.
			</p>
		</div>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 