<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
	<ui:style>
		.answer {
			padding:0 3%;
		}
		
		.question{
			font-weight: bold;
		}
		
		.sectionHeader {
			font-size: 18pt;
			border-bottom:#DDD dotted 4px;
			font-weight: bold;
			padding-bottom: 10px;
		}
	</ui:style>
	<g:HTMLPanel>
		<div id="body-text">
		
			<p class="{style.sectionHeader}">General</p>
		
			<p class="{style.question}">What is BooksPicker?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			It's a service built by MIT students to make book-buying fast and cheap.
			Enter your classes and we'll tell you which books are required and which books
			are just recommended. Pick the books you want to buy and we'll search on multiple
			online stores and on-campus listings to find you the best prices out there.
			We find the cheapest price for your entire book cart, which is often better
			than searching for each book individually.
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">Can I search for regular books not related to my classes?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			Yes. Just type in the ISBN of the book you're looking for in the search box, or
			use keywords to find books by title, author, or subject.
			</p>

			<p class="{style.question}">I can't find the book I'm looking for. Why?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			This probably means Amazon doesn't have the book information, so we don't have it
			either. We know, how can Amazon <i>not</i> have it? Not sure, but it happens.
<!--			A well-known example of this problem is the chemistry book for 3.091.-->
<!--			According to The COOP, the book's ISBN is "9780558333171", yet Amazon yields no-->
<!--			results for that ISBN.-->
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">What is an ISBN? Where can I find it?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			Every book officially published has an "International Standard Book Number" or ISBN.
			The ISBN is a 10 or 13-digit number (old ISBNs were 10 digits) used to uniquely
			identify a book. Typically a book's ISBN-13 will be its ISBN-10 with "978" up front.
			Why? Because "978" is a country code for
			"<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bookland_%28imaginary_place%29" target="_blank">Bookland</a>",
			an imaginary place created to reserve the "978" country code and use it as a prefix
			for all barcode (EAN) identifiers referring to books. Weird, yeah...
			</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			Most books give you the ISBN on the back cover next to the barcode. If that fails,
			check the preamble. The ISBN may include some dashes in between the digits; do not
			include them when performing ISBN searches on our site.
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">Why do you use Facebook for logging in?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			It's easy to integrate and it allows us to do many things, like:
			<ul>
			<li>Verify that you're a real person. We want to protect our buyers from bogus
			sellers and protect our sellers from bogus buyers.</li>
			<li>Better match buyers and sellers. We think you'd rather buy a book from a friend
			or a friend's friend than from a stranger.</li>
			<li>Save you (and us) the hassle of typing a new password, verifying an
			email, etc.</li>
    		</ul>
    		</p>
    		<p class="{style.answer}">
    		Don't worry, we will never post anything to your wall without your permission!
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">Do you make money?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			If you buy locally from another student, <i>we make absolutely no money</i>.
			We're not a middleman, but a service that matches buyers and sellers for free.
			</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			If you buy from certain online stores (e.g., Amazon), we do get a small referral
			fee. Note that the fee comes from the store, not from you, so you end up paying
			the <i>same price</i> that you would've paid had you gone to the store directly. And in
			any case, the revenue is barely enough to cover our hosting and advertising costs.
			By buying the books through us, you're not helping us get rich, but you are
			helping us pay the bills so we can maintain and improve the site!
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">Why don't you add &lt;cool-feature&gt;?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			There's a bunch of features we'd like to add. But we're only 3 busy students doing
			this in our spare time, so things take some time. These are some ideas we have in
			mind, but if you have any other suggestions, do let us know!
			<ul>
			<li>Textbook feedback from other students</li>
			<li>Book rentals</li>
			<li>Integration with libraries</li>
			<li>Fare alerts</li>
			<li>Buy-back search</li>
			<li>Search filters (ala Kayak)</li>
    		</ul>
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">I like BooksPicker, how can I spread the word?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			Tell your friends and 'Like' us on Facebook! (See top left corner!)
			</p>
			
<!--			<p class="{style.question}">Are you going to maintain the site even after you leave MIT?</p>-->
<!--			<p class="{style.answer}">-->
<!--			Yes. We are aware that others have tried to solve the same problem as we do,-->
<!--			but their solutions disappeared once they left MIT. We're committed to make-->
<!--			this work for terms to come, even if we have to recruit a current MIT-->
<!--			undergrad to maintain the site.-->
<!--			</p>-->
			
			<p class="{style.sectionHeader}">Data</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">Where is your book list data coming from? Can I trust it?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
<!--			Primarily, we get the information directly from MIT, from the <i>same source</i> that-->
<!--			Stellar and the course catalog use. You can see the data yourself at the-->
<!--			<a href="http://opendata.mit.edu/~opendata/www/index.php?title=OpenData:Community_Portal" target="_blank">OpenData</a>-->
<!--			repository (requires an MIT certificate).-->
<!--			When MIT has no data for a particular class, we turn to The COOP.-->
			We use a variety of sources, but most of the data comes from your college bookstore.
			They publish the class listings in their online
			<a href="http://bncollege.com/" target="_blank">site</a>.
			If it's not available there, we'll add it manually upon a user's request.
			But who knows, maybe that class simply requires no textbooks!
			</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			So basically, if you can trust the data in your college bookstore,
			you can trust ours. The only caveat is that sometimes we are unable to 'resolve'
			some of the data. That is, we're unable to get the corresponding book
			information from Amazon.
<!--			A well-known example of this is the chemistry book for 3.091, which is a custom MIT book.-->
			This happens rarely though, in maybe about ~1% of the listings.
			</p>
			
<!--			<p class="{style.question}">The course catalog has books listed for x.xxx, but you don't. Why?</p>-->
<!--			<p class="{style.answer}">-->
<!--			The course catalog uses a "fallback" mechanism and they will display data from-->
<!--			prior semesters whenever the data for the current semester is not available.-->
<!--			We do not do that. We only show <i>current</i> Fall 2010 data from MIT, and whenever-->
<!--			that's not available, we show <i>current</i> Fall 2010 data from The COOP. We do this-->
<!--			because we prefer to show no data than to show <i>potentially</i> erroneous data.-->
<!--			We really don't want you to buy a book you don't actually need!-->
<!--			</p>-->
			
			<p class="{style.sectionHeader}">Buying</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">What's special about your BooksPicker cart? Why do you use it?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			A BooksPicker cart is simply a group of books. When we search for the cheapest prices for
			your cart, we actually find the best prices for all possible book <i>combinations</i>. This means
			your total price might be lower than the sum of the individual cheapest price
			for each book in the cart. How? As an example, Amazon may offer free shipping
			on orders over $x. So even if Harry Potter is more expensive at Amazon than it
			is on eBay, it <i>might</i> be better to buy it from Amazon if it helps you put you
			over the $x limit.
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">Which stores do you currently show results from?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			At the moment, we support Amazon, Half (eBay), AbeBooks, and Alibris, but we
			plan to add many more. We also show offers from local students through our local
			sales platform.
<!--			available through-->
<!--			the APO Book Exchange and, of course, our own local sales platform.-->
			</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			In general, we'll try to include any legit online seller. We plan to add the
			following stores in the near future: Biblio, Biggerbooks, eCampus, iChapters,
			Textbooks.com, textbooksrus, and Overstock. Let us know if there's a particular
			source we haven't thought of!
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">What happens when I click 'Buy' on one of your offers?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			If you click on an offer for an external website, we send you to the place where
			you can purchase the offer, whether it be Amazon, eBay, or whomever.
			</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			When you "buy" a local offer from BooksPicker, we'll put you in touch with the
			seller so you can coordinate payment and pickup on your own terms. <i>We don't
			actually handle any money.</i> Our role is to match buyers and sellers for free!
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">Why are AbeBook's prices so low?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			Because they are specialists in selling rare and international editions, so
			chances are the low prices you saw are for international edition books. See the
			"International Editions" section to learn more about what this means.
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.sectionHeader}">Selling</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">Can I sell my books through BooksPicker? How?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			Yes! Click on "sell" and add offer listings for the books you want to sell.
			All you need to have is the book's ISBN, the book's condition, and set a price
			(hint: try our automatic pricing option!).
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">What happens when someone buys my offer?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			You'll receive an email with the buyer's contact information so you can
			coordinate with him/her directly and carry out the transaction. <i>We don't
			actually handle any money.</i> Our role is to match buyers and sellers for
			free!
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">Why does my offer listing expire?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			If you book does not sell within 5 days, we will take it off the listings
			(similar to Craigslist). We don't want out-dated offers lingering around
			in the search results. However, when your offer expires we'll send you a
			notification so you can quickly re-post it if you want to.
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">What is automatic pricing?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			It's a method we created to price for your book for you. All you have to
			do is choose one of the two selling strategies:
			<ul>
			<li>Quickie Sale (recommended): sets the price to be highly competitive
			within the market, making your book sell <i>fast</i>.</li>
			<li>Money Lover: sets the price competitively but not as much. It may take
			longer to sell but you'll get more cash.</li>
			</ul>
			</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			The automatic price will depend on the current market conditions as well
			as the book's condition. Thus, <i>the price today may differ from the price
			tomorrow</i>, but your book will always remain adequately priced!
			</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			And if you're scared that the automatic price might drop too low, you can
			set a lower bound and we'll never sell your book for less than that.
			</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			Don't sell your book for peanuts just to make a quick sale! Try our
			automatic pricing and sell fast <i>and</i> for good value!
			</p>
			
<!--			<p class="{style.question}">Why do you ask for my book's location?</p>-->
<!--			<p class="{style.answer}">-->
<!--			Whenever possible, we'll try to match you with a buyer who is-->
<!--			geographically close to you. We think you prefer to sell to someone in-->
<!--			your dorm than someone across campus!-->
<!--			</p>-->
			
			<p class="{style.question}">How do you use my Facebook information?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			Whenever possible, we'll try to match you with a buyer who is socially
			close to you. We think you prefer to sell to a friend or a friend's
			friend than to a complete stranger!
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">Why should I sell my books at BooksPicker instead of, say, sending an email to my dorm?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			Beside the fact that this service was built specially for you, we think
			you should sell your books through us because:
			<ul>
			<li>We have a bigger audience than your dorm email list has, and you
			can avoid being hated by everyone you just spammed who isn't looking for books.</li>
			<li><i>We do not take a single penny from your sale</i>, unlike most other local
			sales services.</li>
			<li>You can sell fast and get a great return when you use our automatic
			pricing option. And you don't even have to think!</li>
			<li>You'll get buyers who are geographically and socially close to you to
			minimize hassles!</li>
			</ul>
			</p>

			<p class="{style.sectionHeader}">International Editions</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">What's an international edition textbook?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			It's simply the international counterpart to a US edition. Most international
			editions have slightly different covers and many have different ISBNs on the
			outside covers (although some have the same ISBN as the US edition on the inside).
			These books were originally created to be sold in different regions.
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">Why are international editions so much cheaper?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			We don't know, they just are. But textbooks aren't the only things that are
			cheaper overseas than in the US... Can you think of any other examples?
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">Is it legal to buy international editions in the US?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			Yes! Textbook publishers would love to have people think otherwise, but
			courts have time and time again asserted your right to purchase international
			editions. If you don't want to take our word for it, check out this
			<a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2003/10/21/us/students-find-100-textbooks-cost-50-purchased-overseas.html" target="_blank">article</a>.
			</p>
			
			<p class="{style.question}">What risks am I taking by buying international editions?</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			Not many really, but here are some things to consider:
			<ul>
			<li>Though international and US editions are usually <i>exactly the same</i>, word
			for word, page by page, there's a very small chance that they'll have slight
			differences.</li>
			<li>Many times the international edition is paperback, while the US edition is
			hard cover, so watch out for that if you care about it.</li>
			<li>The international edition book will usually (but not always) ship from an
			overseas location, which means the shipping cost <i>might</i> be higher and the
			waiting time <i>might</i> be greater. Of course, the lower price more than makes up
			for it, provided you can wait the extra time (if any).</li>
			</ul>
			</p>
			<p class="{style.answer}">
			We personally think international editions are a great alternative to the
			expensive US editions, but buy at your own risk!
			</p>
			
<!--			<p></p>-->
<!--			<p class="{style.answer}">-->
<!--			</p>-->
<!--			-->
<!--			<p></p>-->
<!--			<p class="{style.answer}">-->
<!--			</p>-->
<!--			-->
<!--			<p></p>-->
<!--			<p class="{style.answer}">-->
<!--			</p>-->
		</div>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 